# **BARBAROS ELDEN**

CLOUD ENGINEER

#### DETAILS

#### ADDRESS

Merkez District Defnebayiri st. No:6 D:6 Sariyer Istanbul, 34453 Turkey

#### PHONE

05313130725

#### EMAIL

barbaroselden@outlook.com

#### DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

08.05.1998 Istanbul

#### DRIVING LICENSE

A2

#### LINKS

https://barbaroselden.tk/

### SKILLS

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

Angular

Python

Node.js

React

Linux

Amazon AWS

Microsoft Azure

Google Cloud

Microsoft Office

Frontend Development

Backend Development

Cybersecurity

#### PROFILE

Ever since I was little, I was interested in how computers work and I tried to improve myself in this field. It has always been captivating for me to read and research documents related to hardware, software and computers, along with the courses I have received online, the software languages IIII have learned, my researches and the projects I have developed as applications. I want to gain experience and contribute to the realization of a project. I want to continue my career and life as a software developer and IT. The biggest feature that I have been playing chess for years and the department I have been reading has been the development of my analytical intelligence. In this way, I learned to solve complex problems in the shortest way and to develop a different perspective in the face of problems. I am extremely open to learning, development, criticism and group work. I am doing my best to improve and raise myself and I will continue to do so.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

## Frontend Web Developer, Varsapp

Mar 2021 - Jun 2021

#### Licensed Chess Arbiter, Turkey Chess Federation

2018 - Present

# Chess Trainer, Private College and Public Schools

2018 - Present

I worked at Private Cent College and Ismail Erez Primary School and Ferit Aysan Primary School. I'm still working at Private Cent College.

#### EDUCATION

# Bachelor of Science in Physics (eng), Yildiz Technical University

2019 - Present

I'm a senior and I will be gruaduating in 2023.

# Bachelor of Science in Chemistry (eng), Hacettepe University

2017 - 2018

Since the department didn't unleash my potential so I switched to the Physics department because I wanted to study in a numerically heavier department that covered most of the engineering fields and aroused my curiosity.

## Primary and Highschool (%100 scholarship), Private Cent College

2009 - 2017

The school provides education in English.

#### LANGUAGES

English

....

French

. . . . .

#### HOBBIES

Playing guitar and drums, Reading books, Music, Drawing, Handball, Chess, Travelling

#### COURSES

# Google Cloud Server, Google

2022 - 2022

# Introduction to Digital Art, Cubebrush

2021 - 2021

## Amazon AWS, Amazon

2022 - 2022

# Web Pentesting, Udemy

2019 - 2019

## Phyton 101, Udemy

2019 - 2019

# **Linux Command Line, Yildiz Technical University**

2018 - 2018

## Chess Arbiter License, Chess Federation

2017 - 2017

# Web Development, Udemy

2019 - 2019

## REFERENCES

# **Cem Yildirim from Next Generation Technology**

0532 602 03 65

## Metin Celik from Lal Organization and Sports Services

0532 440 91 66

## Özlem Sarac from Retired Customs Broker

0532 528 10 12